<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Pete Myron</title>
    <link>https://petemyron.github.io/index.html</link>
    <description>PETE MYRON Hey there! I’m a super versatile techy with almost 20 years of experience creating cool telemetry and monitoring systems, integrating services, and making things better in general. I love diving deep into any topic, whether it’s technical or not, just to learn something new. I’m always curious and love exploring new things. I can speak both nerd and business, so I’m great at bridging the gap between the two to help solve problems. Whether it’s managing staff or writing code myself, I’m happy to take on any workload.</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://petemyron.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>https://petemyron.github.io/about-me/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://petemyron.github.io/about-me/index.html</guid>
      <description>Hi! I’m an extremely versatile and a quick learner with 20 years of experience creating patented telemetry and monitoring systems, integrating services, and efficiently creating value on anything I touch. I will go deep on any subject of interest, whether it’s technical or not, just to learn something new. Curiosity is a daily adventure for me. I’m equally comfortable speaking nerd or business and can thread the needle between the two to help solve problems. I’m happy to manage the workloads of staff or commit code myself.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Work Experience</title>
      <link>https://petemyron.github.io/experience/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://petemyron.github.io/experience/index.html</guid>
      <description>Sr. Site Reliability Engineer, Developer Portal, Electronic Arts – since 2023 Led platform reliability and developer experience initiatives across testing, CI/CD, observability, documentation, and GitOps. Designed scalable infrastructure and tools to improve platform adoption, developer velocity, and system visibility.&#xA;Achieved 100% uptime on user-facing tools Expanded automated test coverage from ~10% to 70%, growing tests to 500+ assertions Improved CI/CD efficiency by 30% through pipeline and test optimization, accelerating feedback loops for developers Delivered a multi-Argo CD integration, enabling multi-cluster GitOps visibility and onboarding disparate, high-profile teams Implemented unified search and indexing across catalog entities and TechDocs Developed a reusable GitLab CI stage to let partner teams publish documentation to Backstage automatically Created a UI form for editing Backstage entity metadata, simplifying onboarding for TechDocs and Argo CD annotations Principal Software Engineer, Customer Experience Lab, T-Mobile – 2019 Managed team of engineers for daily lifecycle of group’s main products, determining broad strategy and prioritizing tasks. Handled service design, security, and compliance of all aspects. Recommended policy changes and contributed to policy documentation. Conducted independent study and prototyping of potential new systems, services, methods, and frameworks in areas of generative AI, AR/VR, and accessibility.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Skills</title>
      <link>https://petemyron.github.io/skills/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://petemyron.github.io/skills/index.html</guid>
      <description>I possess a wide range of skills that make me a valuable asset to any development team. My proficiency in programming languages such as Python, Ruby, and Go, as well as some Android/Java and iOS development, allows me to develop and maintain complex applications with ease. I am also experienced in working with monitoring and visualization tools such as Grafana, InfluxDB/TICK, Elastic Stack, and Prometheus, which enables me to monitor and analyze system performance effectively. Additionally, my expertise in containerization with Docker and cloud computing with AWS allows me to deploy and manage applications in a scalable and efficient manner. I have a lot of telemetry and system monitoring expereicne. I’m a highly effective communicator and can solve problems autonomously, ensuring that projects are delivered on time and within budget. I am naturally curious and always eager to learn new technologies and techniques, which makes me a valuable member of any team.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>https://petemyron.github.io/projects/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://petemyron.github.io/projects/index.html</guid>
      <description>Check out some of the awesome projects I’ve worked on over the past few years. Most can be found on Github&#xA;Device MatrixRemote, real device access and automation&#xA;SitespeedA website performance monitoring tool&#xA;Generative AIProjects with Aritificial Intelligence&#xA;Other StuffInventions galore!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patents</title>
      <link>https://petemyron.github.io/patents/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://petemyron.github.io/patents/index.html</guid>
      <description>PATENTS I am passionate about inventing things, most recently in the domains of telemetry, automation, and accessibility. I love taking an idea and turning it into a prototype and refining it until it becomes of obvious value. It’s incredibly satisfying to see my ideas come to life and make a positive impact on people’s lives. I believe that technology can be used to make the world a better place, and I’m always looking for ways to use my skills to create innovative solutions that improve people’s lives. Whether it’s developing new tools to help make things more accessible, automating tedious tasks to save time and increase efficiency, or using telemetry to gather data and improve performance, I’m always excited to explore new possibilities and push the boundaries of what’s possible.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>